filehippo.com 2019-12-31

# FileHippo Privacy Policy - FileHippo.com

FileHippo s.r.o. ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. FileHippo is one of our trading names.

This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to in our terms of use and this policy) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting filehippo.com you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

## Information We May Collect From You

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  *  **Information you give us.** You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our site www.filehippo.com (our site) or by corresponding with us by e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you subscribe to our service, search for a product, participate in discussion boards or other social media functions on our site, enter a competition, promotion or survey, and when you report a problem with our site. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and in some cases phone number
  *  **Information we collect about you.** With regard to each of your visits to our site we may automatically collect the following information: 
    * technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, platform and device identifier (or "UDID")
    * information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service number.
This information does not, however, identify you by name, and it is not necessary for you to provide us with your name or address to use our site.
  *  **Information we receive from other sources.** We are also working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers and search information providers) and may receive information about you from them.

## Cookies

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them (including how we and our partners collect information via the cookies that our used on our website)see our Cookie policy.

## Uses Made of the Information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  *  **Information you give to us.** We will use this information: 
    * to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us;
    * to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about;
    * to provide you with information about goods or services we feel may interest you. Except with your agreement, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to or enquiry from you. If we ever propose to allow selected third parties to contact you by electronic means with information about other goods or services that may interest you, we will seek your consent;
    * to notify you about changes to our service;
    * to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer. 
  * **Information we collect about you.** We will use this information: 
    * to administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
    * to improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer; 
    * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
    * as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure;
    * to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;
    * to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about goods or services that may interest you or them.
  *  **Information we receive from other sources.** We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may us this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).

## Disclosure of Your Information

We may share your personal information with any member of our group, including our affiliate companies.

We may share your information with selected third parties including:

  * Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you.
  * Advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. We do not disclose information that identifies you by name or provides your address to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 500 men aged under 30 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, women in London). We may make use of the data we have collected from you that does not identify you by name to enable us to comply with our advertisers' wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.
  * Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our site. 

We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of FileHippo s.r.o., our customers, or others. 

## Where We Store Your Personal Data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect any data you provide to us, or we obtain about you, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## Your Rights

Where we process your personal data, you have the right to ask us not to process that personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your personal data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes and will seek your agreement if we intend to disclose your personal data to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at privacy@filehippo.comprivacy@filehippo.com.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check this page frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.

## Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to privacy@filehippo.com
